

# MERT ARAR

WEB DEVELOPER FRONT-END



## CONTACT



Phone

(+90) 554 547 08 81



**Email** 

mertarar.ma@gmail.com



Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in, mert-arar-6788771bb/



Portfolio

https://www.mertarar.com



Github

https://github.com/MertArar



**EDUCATION** 

2017-2023

 Bachelor Of Software Engineering

Atılım University

2013- 2017 High School

Özel Diltaş Anadolu Lisesi



LANGUAGE

- English (B2 Upper Intermediate)
- Turkish (Native)



# **SUMMARY**

I graduated from Atılım University, Department of Software Engineering. I have work experience and extensive training in software design and development. I act according to strong business ethics and correct communication strategies in team or individual environments to increase product success and process efficiency. With our analytical thinking, I am improving myself in troubleshooting, problem solving and professional time management. If you ask me, the trait I value most in myself is ambition, because I never give up on things and continue to the end without giving up on learning.



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Intern - Front-End Web DeveloperB12 İnteraktif Bilişim

July 2022 - Oct 2022

I took part in website development with the VueJS framework. I improved my knowledge of HTML, CSS and JavaScript. At the end of the internship, I took part in the front-end part of the project developed.

# Chief of Front-End - Flutter Developer SpeakSTU

Dec 2021 - July 2022

I worked as the front-end chief of the social media mobile application project developed as a crossplatform with Flutter. I was among the founders of this social media application, which uses the Agile software development method.

# Intern - Web/Mobile Developer PigaSoft

July 2021 - Sep 2021

During my internship, I gained knowledge and experience in HTML, CSS text processing languages and Javascript programming language. I was also a full-stack developer and I developed a website with using HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP.

#### Freelance Web Developer

Nov 2020 - present

I have been providing web development services as a freelancer for over 3 years. I am developing websites with ReactJS.



#### **MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE**

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

ReactJS

VueJS

Flutter / Dart

Project Management

C, C#, C++



## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

ATAG Atılım Researchers Day Participant (05/2022 - Present)

Business Idea Competition 2nd Winner - SpeakSTU Mobile Application

Atılım Software Engineering Society (ASES) (09/2018 - 06/2020)

• Board Member - Software Manager